(Han Seok-kyu)
(Pei Xiancheng)
(Li Rui)
(President Shin Project)
(This drama is purely fictional
Appearing characters, place names, institutions)
(Events, groups and occupations, etc.
All have nothing to do with reality (I hereby inform you)
(Child actors are all accompanied by their guardians
Photographed in a safe environment)
I don’t know who hurt my sister
(Review of the previous episode)
uncle
Help me find that person and teach him a lesson
Schwinn
You have been airborne these days
Let's go deliver food together with the troops.
If that unreasonable
What did the guest do to Shi On?
Please contact me immediately
Being involved with him will give you a headache
Don't fight him
There's someone inside
Cao Bili
airborne troops
How bold you dare to touch my employees
Master Jin, help me find someone.
Cui Xiongzhi
Three-term city councilor
Because his father's power is above the law
How about you want to negotiate with me?
Still...
I really want to be...
Threatening to take a look?
(President Shin Project)
Oh my God, that's Schwinn's motorcycle.
(Episode 5)
Schwinn
Cui Yongpal
you crazy
let me go
Is this guy definitely dead?
Hey don't worry
My dad will help me sort it out.
This is obviously a threat
Oops, Congressman
What kind of threat is so scary?
All I want is negotiation, negotiation
This is an illegal recording file
It can't be used as evidence for the verdict.
Who would use this kind of thing in court?
Mainly used in TV stations, right?
For example, in "Live Chase"
In current affairs programs such as "Traces"
Use the power of society to conduct public trials
Don't you want to negotiate?
Why do you keep threatening me?
How about it? Do you have any other evidence?
If you have any, take it out and take a look.
Any other evidence?
My staff a few days ago
I was almost crushed to death in a car slaughterhouse.
Oops
Do you want to take a look?
Let me see
You see...
what is this
Of course you don't know
What about this?
My employee passed out in front of this house.
Then when I woke up, I was already at Fu Heng Car Park.
Just this car
It was also from this house that we drove to Fu Heng Car Park.
And when my employees wake up
Found myself in the boot of a car being scrapped
It's not easy...
I managed to save my life with great difficulty
Then what?
what
So you think this car is related to me?
I didn't say that
How about it, Congressman?
Is there any connection?
I...
I am a person who distinguishes between public and private matters
Although our Long Min is a little ignorant,
But when his backer cleans up the aftermath for him
I won't do this kind of thing
If people show kindness
You should accept kindness
what are you doing
Why are you still threatening me?
Oops, what about this?
There is a fine line between threats and negotiations.
The bad guy may sound like a threat
But good guys sound like they're negotiating
It's all like this
OK then
Let's deal with it according to the law.
I have a public official position
I have to participate in this election again
You came here because you wanted to take advantage of the opportunity to blackmail me, right?
Don't accuse good people casually
Go back
Go back and make better fried chicken
Is it more delicious?
yes
Excuse me
By the way, Congressman
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
It turns out you have eaten my fried chicken before
Welcome to call again
This case will be widely
Tong is charged with committing car arson
I want to add the content of the lawsuit
In addition to ordinary car arson
There is also property damage
Violence
Please add the crime of insult too.
The place where the motorcycles are parked is a business district
A little careless
The fire will spread to surrounding buildings
May cause large fires
What nonsense are you talking about?
Hey you crazy person
Are you a food delivery person?
And the suspect
I was also bullied
The victim ordered takeout for this purpose
Then maliciously looking for trouble or beating the victim
Is he your lawyer?
He is my employee
uncle
President
You are not injured, right?
No, everything is fine
How?
What can you do if you stare at me?
Mr. Cui Longmin
People who do business these days know more about the law.
Your employees are smart
As the president, you should feel at ease, right?
Yes
Very practical
Long Min
You look a lot like your dad
Shi-on knocked him down?
Yes
You did a good job with what I taught you.
You don't study, why don't you just teach her how to fight?
No...
Not like that
I asked him to teach him
But Long Ba
Will it be out soon?
Relying on his father's background
Arson is a felony and the sentence can only be actual punishment.
According to Article 166 Paragraph 1 of the Criminal Code
punishable by imprisonment for more than two years
Even if it is a sincere reflection
Getting leniency would also be a reprieve.
To put it simply, it's not that easy for him to come out
So Shi On, you don’t have to worry
How could you not worry?
He even set the motorcycle on fire
This is about my livelihood
It'll be fine if you're not hurt, Shi Wen
Let's go together
You go back first
where are you going
I want to look for additional evidence
Just one crime of arson still doesn't make you feel at ease.
He has committed many crimes
I want to find someone who can testify
Do you want me to go with you?
No need. I can go by myself.
I set off
Pay attention to safety
Long Min never did that kind of thing to me
please don't contact me again
I'm not familiar with him. Sorry.
Do you know Guo Xianyu?
Is this someone who has lived here before?
I just moved here last year
What brings you here?
I'm looking for someone who moved around here last year
It's about school bullying
Is it school bullying?
The student's name is...
What the hell is going on?
Congressman, please come this way
That...
No one hurt?
What are the losses?
Don’t you know after watching it?
My employee's motorcycle was burned down
People in the business district almost got into trouble
sorry
But the more serious loss is
My employees were threatened by your son.
sorry
It's because I didn't educate my children well
That's why I caused you so much trouble
I will compensate for the losses as much as possible
If you cause losses to others, you should be compensated.
It's like you're showing mercy
Let's go Schwinn
Good
really sorry
Congressman, let's go in first.
Let me explain to you
OK let's go
Sorry
Dad looks obviously normal
Who does Long Ba look like?
That's what it looks like
Who else can I look like?
Of course he's like his father
There's no need to come out. It's okay.
Oops, Boss Quan
Although the same is true for other things
But children are really beyond our control
You are right, yes
Oops
How dare you be so arrogant with that look?
This stinky boy, stand still for me
Stand still, you guy
stand still
come here
(Future Leap Forward Party)
Forget it
Hello
What about me...
Have you been told to keep an eye on our Long Min?
1 billion?
I'm really going to die
Just to bail out a moron with no criminal record.
It actually costs 1 billion
Look at it this way
Prosecutor Zhang is also a gangster, right?
Right?
(Later entering the business district)
Hello airborne troops
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
Is it going well to find the evidence this morning?
I got a bunch of clues
Or only some
I met Cui Yongmin
Victims of school bullying
Although not everyone makes it clear
But I'm looking for the exact witness
Where is the president?
Huh?
Didn't you say you would use your own method to solve it?
I've always done it my own way.
catch
But why for me...
Do you have to walk to deliver food?
Give Schwinn the car keys tomorrow.
What?
Was this given to Choi Yong-min by his father?
What are you saying, kid?
Otherwise...
Ah, is it Shi On’s birthday present?
I bought this with my own money
That's weird. It's rented.
But how do you know Shi On’s birthday?
Didn’t you tell me about it at the last dinner party?
It's her birthday in two weeks
do i have
But having said that...
I was curious about one thing before
What's going on
Why does the president take so much care of Shi On?
Why else? Look here
Whether it's the laundry, Pluto
It's still my shop
Don’t we all have to rely on takeout to make ends meet?
So... Schwinn's motorcycle
It's our source of livelihood
Am I right?
Hello airborne troops
This is what I'm thinking
Shi Wen shouldn’t know that, right?
Not really
Huh? Too obvious
Is it obvious?
Abominable
Anyway, airborne troops, you should be more careful.
Once you fall in love with Shi On
You have no way to escape
Did you sleep well last night?
Why are you pretending to be cool in front of other people’s houses?
Of course I'm waiting for you
I've been waiting for an hour
What?
are you stupid
why don't you call me
I'm afraid of waking you up
The president only said early morning but not the time.
Uncle?
Hurry up and go deliver food.
Not faster
Fast and safe
Where did the motorcycle come from?
The president gave it to me last night
This is indeed what an uncle would do
By the way...
Where did you go after leaving the police station yesterday?
many places
Didn't I say that?
I'll find proof
The person who did what Choi Yong-min did
Why spend so much
Are you thinking too much about Long Ba?
A judge once said this
(Cao Bili)
what
Are you kidding?
Whoever jokes on a friend will push him to the side of the road
(Bench)
Spit on him as he falls to the ground
And took all the money in the wallet
(Protective juvenile seat)
you two
They were all sentenced to punishment No. 10
How do you beat people?
The law will come back on you
Use fines and sentences
This kind of world is fair
Your Honor
Let my son go for once
No I won't let him go
You should look at the kid next to you
instead of begging me
Ask him how he should treat his friends
What can be done and what cannot be done
This court hearing ends here
adjourn
Is that why you want to be a judge?
It's one of the reasons
What's important
Let Cui Yongmin get the punishment he deserves
Only then can we give justice to the victims
He must understand
If you deprive others of their happiness
Your own happiness will also be taken away
This is the way of the world
(Fresh Cream Cake View Gifts
open card)
what is this
Let’s eat with my mother-in-law and Ye-yeon
thank you
Really
What are you doing looking so handsome so early in the morning?
Handsome?
Are you talking about me?
No, I mean the judge
This is the address of Guo Xianyu’s mother
Thanks to the school too
I don't know where they moved to.
I checked
The case of classmate Guo Xianyu
It ended with simple suicide
I'm so sad to hear that
How painful is his mother?
Anyway, I'll go take a look first.
walk slowly
hello
My name is Cao Bili
You are Guo Xianyu’s...
Mom, right?
Wait...
I'm back
Where did you go?
It's obviously me who's working hard
Why are you so weak?
I went to see Cui Yongmin
Mother of bullying victim
What?
When he was in his sophomore year of high school
Transferred to another school because he was bullied by Choi Yong-min
In the end, I made an extreme choice
dead?
Because I feel so wronged
Only then would you make that choice?
What did his mother say?
she has nothing to say
I told her that Cui Yongmin had been arrested.
But she said it didn't make any sense
So you came back?
yes
first day of negotiation
It was like the first day of school
You have to listen to what the other person is saying and observe at the same time
Then find out where the other party's flaws lie
What do you think when we first met?
What's most important?
Let the other person trust you
It seems I didn't do this
in order to do this
Even if it's a bluff
You have to show it too
Make the other person feel comfortable
I am a trustworthy person
Show it to your aunt?
Of course
Now go and show your sincerity
Only in this way will she have the strength to continue fighting.
I'm going out
Hello
Airborne troops, I'm not done yet...
The next part is the key point
aunt
Uncle...
Why are you here again?
Don't look at me like this. I'm a good fighter.
I am a 3rd Dan Taekwondo and 2nd Dan Kendo
if you want to see
I can also demonstrate it on the spot.
I didn't mean to fight
I am very good at reading
Graduated first in the police academy
He also passed the judge appointment examination with first place.
I work so hard
Just to catch a guy like Choi Yong-min
Aunt, please believe me
The injustice suffered by Hyun Woo
I will definitely seek justice for him
This is Hyun Woo's diary
thank you
So the guy said he was willing to testify?
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
If you know the sincerity of your deceased friend
It should touch his heart.
What if he's indifferent?
What?
If the world is really so beautiful
What do you think of the Longba family?
Will the guy still look like that?
He didn’t just bully Shi On
It almost killed you
Have you forgotten
So we need to collect evidence slowly...
How can I have time to slowly defeat those bad guys?
Oh, I was really
don’t want to do this step
What are you going to do?
do big things
Do big things?
Coming
I'm going to do something big
Yesterday afternoon at the shopping street parking lot
A man in his 20s named Cui
Set fire to a motorcycle and try to escape
Finally, he was captured by the joint efforts of the citizens present.
The incident that almost caused a fire
The suspect was identified as
The son of the current MP Xian City Councilor
Oh my god
What should I do?
That family is so unlucky
The children are simply enemies.
Oh, it's true
It's weird that everyone always just blames the kids
It is those parents who make their children enemies.
Yes
Brother, you are right
eldest sister
Suppose there is only one box of chocolate milk in this store
will you sell it to me
Or sell it to Representative Choi?
What?
Is this a test on me?
Yes
Oops
Of course I will sell it to you, brother
Right?
Yes
That city councilor never
Never bought chewing gum in our store
Why do you ask even though you know it?
What do you think I am?
Come and wish you a prosperous business
OK
I'm leaving
Please walk slowly Okay
President Zhang, do you know Representative Choi Woong-sik?
Representative Choi?
Right
The guy who bullied Shi On
That's his son
His son must be punished
But Representative Choi is a good person
Can the food be served quickly?
OK
Is he a good person?
How is that person doing?
After the COVID-19 epidemic is over
Small businessman who opens his own shop
When households one after another cannot survive and close down
Please use it slowly
President Zhang
Regional currency has now been issued
The situation should gradually improve
Let's work hard together
Come on
Come on, President Zhang, come on
Grants and tax relief
It was all promoted by Representative Choi
You also open your own store, so you should know it very well, right?
I don’t know. I was a homeless person at that time.
Speaking of which, President Zhang
Do you support me or Congressman Choi?
What's there to ask?
Of course it is better to have closer neighbors
Are you serious?
Yes
I got one vote for now
This child really makes his father embarrassed.
Could it be that his father failed to educate his child well?
Representative Choi is not that kind of person
If it weren't for him, I would have been kicked out long ago
Everyone, calm down first
President Kim, please listen to me carefully.
Although the contract has expired
But you can't be casual
Tell the bosses present to leave.
before the rebuilding project begins
You have to prioritize these people here
Representative Choi called President Kim over
Let him sign in front of us
He is a city councilman that I recognize
Oh my, what's there to recognize?
So you support me
Or do you support Congressman Choi?
What about you, President Shen?
Do you support me or Congressman Choi?
What's there to ask?
Of course I support you
Compared to Representative Choi
Of course I support you too
Are you satisfied?
What do you think of me wearing this outfit?
What?
Dear business friends from backward business circles
and the folks from Ma Xian City
There are also VIPs who came here specially
Thank you very much for coming
He's pretending like this
What do you want to say?
Although everyone is busy at work
Came here specially
I'm so grateful
I ran a fried chicken restaurant there
Shin Jae-yi who has been frying chicken
Today I solemnly announce to you that
I will officially run for election as a member of Ma Xian City Council
Did you already know this?
Coming
I'm going to do something big
What he calls a big deal
Everyone
Our business district and horses
Xian City is now in crisis
It's getting harder to make ends meet
Business is gradually getting worse
It can be said that we can’t see the future at all.
If you continue to sit here and wait for death
None of us can survive
So I am Shen Zaiyi
For all the small merchants present
Put forward five visions
And these five visions
I will definitely
I will definitely find a way to promote it
OK, please give me a round of applause.
Brother, you are great
So what are these five visions?
First Brother, where are you going?
Let's live together
second
We must live together even if we die
third
no matter what happens
We all need to live together
Oops, my throat hurts so much
Are you really planning to run?
Didn't I make it very clear?
Okay, even if you really want to run
Who will vote for you?
Is anyone born to be a city councilor?
I added the businesses nearby
At least a hundred votes are guaranteed
I will also vote for uncle
I will be your support club president
Don't worry about funds
Really? Hello, President
Really, brother, please stop fanning the flames, okay?
You don't live here
I don’t have the right to vote, but I still encourage him.
You really are too
Anyone can participate in the election
As a judge, don’t you even understand this?
But why did you decide to run?
Because I am Choi Woong Sik’s strongest opponent
If uncle can replace
Long Ba’s father was elected city councilor
that would be great
Although I also hope that Representative Choi will lose the election, but...
Have you forgotten your duty?
No
Brother, why are you here to cause trouble?
What's wrong
hate showing face
President Shin who avoids crowded places
Say you want to run for election?
why
After all, city councilors are powerful
My son committed school bullying
Even violence can be suppressed
Press down what?
He can cover up all the wrong things with one hand
Brother, I do it too
You do this to protect your family
But you don’t have to run for election.
The other party is a current city councilor
Of course I want to be in the same position as him
It's fun to fight
Based on the judge's ethics program
Neither Bili nor I can help you.
Do I need your help?
I've already planned it
I want to propose five visions
This is good
Good
Once again
five items
Let's go to the next place
(2Li Guangwen
Kwon Bongqin 3 4 Jin Wanjae)
I can't stand it. It's really annoying.
(Bulldozer-like execution!)
Really good
(That would be so lucky
Make your child’s future smooth and smooth)
(No party membership Quan Qifeng 7)
What is he doing?
This is my seventh challenge
I was 28 years ago
The boss made up his mind when he was born
To create a place that allows
A world where children live a good life
before I accomplish this mission
Never give up
President Shin, let’s have a healthy competition.
Really
(Shin Jae-yi knows how to listen)
bring about change)
Bringing Change Candidate 9)
Please vote for candidate No. 1. Thank you.
(Look over here Look over here No. 1)
Hello OMG...thank you
How are you doing?
I heard your son got into trouble?
I can't even take care of my own family.
Do you still dare to stand for election?
you people
Which family doesn’t have a troubled child?
Come and show me
It's also a blessing to Representative Totri that he doesn't have it.
By the way, Congressman
Is Jangseokdong definitely going to be developed?
Of course
Everyone, my most important political opinion
It is to develop into a more prosperous Ma Xian City
I will definitely make your life better
From now on, you will have no worries about food and clothing
Choi Woong Sik...
Whether to vote or not. Whether to vote or not...
Don't vote for Show
Local elections finally begin
(Local Election D14)
Let’s learn about each now
Current status of support in each region
First, let’s take a look at Ma Xian City
This time he is also a current city councilor
Candidate Choi Woong-sik
and candidate Quan Fengqin
These two candidates are the most popular
Candidate No. 3 Quan Fengqin
People's support rate is 31%
Following closely behind candidate Choi Woong-sik
(1Choi Woong-sik 43%)
If we can continue to rally voters
It feels like it’s worth a try
Leading candidate Choi Woong-sik
Currently leading by 12%
Even if the voters of candidate Quan Fengqin are more united
Can it change the situation?
It's really curious
"When I feel wronged and depressed, No. 9 Shin Jae-yi"
"No. 9 Shin Jae-yi"
Candidate No. 9 Shin Jae-yi
Candidate No. 9 is the owner of a fried chicken restaurant
His approval rating is less than 1%
There should be no need to mention him in particular.
(9Shen Zaiyi 0.8%)
But it’s better to talk about it
Don’t talk about the candidates yet
Among his campaign aides
A well-known food company president appeared
That one should be more famous, right?
Is that really the case?
Chairman Park Myung-jin of Cheonjin Foods
Although this is the president of a large company
But he even came to help with election support activities
I think these two were in the past
There must be some special origin
No. 9 Shen Zaiyi
"Candidate No. 7 Kwon Qifeng No. 7"
"Hands raised to the iron"
"Ironize your clothes for everyone"
"Candidate No. 9 Shin Jae-yi" Shin Jae-yi
"Candidate No. 9 Shin Jae-yi"
Candidate No. 9 Shin Jae-yi Shin Jae-yi
"Candidate No. 7 Kwon Qifeng No. 7"
So naive
(Candidate No. 7)
"Kwon Qifeng No. 7"
"Quan Qifeng"
Qifeng...
Quan Qifeng
The next one is candidate No. 7 Quan Qifeng
Candidate Kwon Qifeng is
The legend of local elections in Ma Xian City
This is the seventh time in nearly thirty years
This candidate always stops at running
His approval rating is 1%
Thirty years of words
representing him from the millennium
Registration has started since then
Yes
This perseverance should be seen by everyone
"Changes in Political Generations by Li Guangwen"
Candidates in this local election have very different styles
There are also many in Ma Xian City
Candidates offer unique political views
That's right. Oh my God.
Minister Yes
We did a great job choosing lemon yellow this time
Yes, really beautiful
You mean you want to go to the park, right?
Then I'll go there first. Okay
I'll follow soon
Really, he even wore a vest
Aren't you usually bitter rivals?
but except me
No one will help him
Really
I'm afraid the dough will burn
So I brought some dumplings and bread over here
Take it quickly
I also want to participate in the election campaign
Then I won't be polite. Okay
Let's share these among everyone.
Okay, we will enjoy it, uncle
Uncle...
What's going on? Is anyone hurt?
Uncle, look at this quickly
What?
What's this?
"I got food poisoning after eating fried chicken"
How could...
What happened to him?
President
Come to the store quickly
What? Now?
Guys, I really feel betrayed.
I couldn't sleep all night last night
I also helped to promote that the fried chicken here is delicious.
Someone actually got food poisoning
My chicken
He is really gurgling
So I came to the scene
Prepare to report this store
Currently regulated by the Food and Drug Administration
People from the department have already gone in
Let's go in and have a look too
Even Gu Gu Gu came
Does the representative really have a problem?
Really? That’s right
I think he should be running for city council
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
Only then would they not care about the hygiene in the store at all
let's take a look
Please see
Cooking oil is very clean
(domestic chicken)
Qualified
Fresh broccoli Qualified
(CCTV health inspection)
no doubt
(Qualified)
Thank you for your hard work
OK thank you
what do i see now
Have a nice day
Okay please walk slowly
Everyone, this incident is
In order to let me Shin Jae-yi on the 9th
lost this election
The opposition camp’s smear campaign against me
We must take this opportunity to change this unhealthy trend
Myself, No. 9 Shen Zaiyi
We will definitely make changes, everyone.
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
Please go back
Thank you for your hard work, Shi Wen.
uncle
this photo
what
Wait what is this
Look at your hands in the mirror
Have a tattoo?
I saw it yesterday when I was delivering food
Because it was my first time delivering food there
So I remember it very clearly
Really?
what is that place
Oops, sorry
I heard you had food poisoning?
This chicken is freshly fried, don't worry
Enjoy with peace of mind
By the way, Schwinn
OK
There's also this for you to wait for after you finish eating
Read it slowly again
what is this
indictment
Indictment for defamation and false accusation
Hello Schwinn
These two crimes combined
How much is the fine?
Defamation is punishable by imprisonment for up to five years
Deprivation of public rights for less than ten years
Or a fine of less than 10 million yuan
Then false accusation
Fixed-term imprisonment of not more than ten years
If there is a fine...
1000...
5 million yuan?
How many chickens do these add up to?
That's right
Please use it slowly
Let's go
Boss, wait a minute
What happened
do you have something to say
Say it
K soup rice
Just like what my mother cooked for me
That bowl of warm soup
And that bowl of white rice
To me it is the taste of incomparable happiness
Hello?
Hello
How can I...
I don't always only know how to eat
I only eat three meals a day
I don’t ask for my meal money from you.
Why do you dislike me so much?
I have read the diary
But I'm afraid I won't be able to testify in court
Although I'm sorry for Hyunwoo
But even if you do that
Hyun Woo will not be resurrected either
sorry
please wait a moment
I remembered that time
I really hope someone can help me
(Cao Bili)
Fortunately, there are people like that around me
I hope Qinghuan can become
For Hyun-woo, someone like that
Because I have experienced it myself, I understand
Could it be that Long Ba’s father instigated it?
to win the election
President
It's crazy
Wearing shoes and entering someone else's house
I heard that Qinghuan’s father
Received the money for my grandmother's medical expenses
So I can't appear in court to testify.
These pictures are exaggerated
How will the sentence be calculated?
According to Article 11 of the Criminal Code
Article 5, Item 1: Crime of destruction of evidence
will be sentenced to fixed-term imprisonment of not more than five years
Or a fine of not more than 7 million won
But if you go to court
Maybe it won't be that easy
Oops, so tired
give me a cup of coffee
You are here
Uncle Gold Master
Hello Shi Wen
Long time
no see
long time no see
You look very fashionable
Sure enough, only masters can understand masters.
Hello, I took annual leave
To track Alab
Or that guy from Ulab?
It’s super hard
Master Jin, what do you mean?
Right here...
here start from here
"The boss came suddenly"
"I said I was going to a dinner party."
"So I went to eat Jeju pork belly"
"After eating eight servings that day"
"I even moved the car with a forklift."
"Then when compressing"
"A man ran out of the trunk of the car"
This...
I'm just talking about assistant, right?
Yes Yes
And then there are
"Are you still an illegal immigrant?"
"Hey, you are staying illegally too, right?"
"I got permanent residency"
"Our boss's friend is a city councilman"
"He did it for me"
This is already conclusive evidence, right?
That's right
But he didn't name him
Which city councilman is the boss's friend?
In other words, even though there is so much evidence that it is overwhelming
But I can't give a fatal blow.
yes
Fried chicken post because the person who gave the money is anonymous
So it's hard to find a correlation
As for the video of destroying evidence
It is said that it was requested by Qinghuan
may be used to change the accountability framework
So more evidence is needed
What about the slaughterhouse?
It must be found out that Choi Woong-sik is the mastermind behind the scenes
Only in this way can we ensure that Cui
Long Min will also be punished for sure
So except for that trick
There is no other way
I want to stick to it
election
come to you
(Daren Laundry)
When sitting down, be careful not to get chewing gum on you
when greeting people
Be careful not to get makeup
difficult to clean
I only have this set of clothes
I've made you work hard to do laundry.
Thank you, brother
He also lent election clothing to competitors...
This dress is too flashy
Next time, just be like me and wear something simple
This vest has been worn three elections
It's a new vest made when I ran for the fifth time.
Use everything to show off.
But brother
you...
Who do you see as your competition?
Let me think about it...
Although my son may be a little dangerous
However, Choi Woong-sik was elected
The possibility is still the highest
critical moment
He will definitely coordinate to qualify and gather votes
Coordinate to qualify?
Yeah, he's good at winning people over.
So what about candidate Quan Fengqin?
His approval rating is also very high, right?
This person is very good, very good
But he is too idealistic
So I think not
(Proof of document delivery)
Candidate This is proof of delivery of documents
Please come up with serious information
instead of those threatening files
Please explain first why you should
Designated as an ecological environment
Ma Dongshan in the border area was downgraded
Even spray herbicides
Please explain the reason in detail first
Ma Xianshi, please explain it clearly to me.
Make it clear...
Explain clearly the reason for developing Feldspar Cave...
Construction companies and municipal governments
Will it just be a show?
Pretending to be dealing with it
How is it possible
I've been doing this hard work for ten years
You should have become rich a long time ago, right?
if elected
He is really the kind of person who works hard
But Choi Woong-sik and I are here
This time I can probably only finish third at most.
What does your expression mean?
(Daren Laundry)
Whether it’s candidate Quan or me
In order to make Ma Xian City more livable
Now is not the time
Yes, look
if we become one
Gather your strength
What else can't be done?
Regions can grow two or three times faster
Candidate Choi
The development I conceived
Not from destroying nature
However, benefits derived from evicting residents
Coexistence and common prosperity is my ideal development
As expected
Our candidates are indeed young people
Then
Then we are the only ones left behind
sorry
I can't seem to cooperate with you
farewell
Abominable
Give me the cigarette
Anyway, the permission has been issued
There's no need to keep arguing with him
Just flatten this place
You may think that Members support
The holding rate is rising slower than expected
That's why he hesitated
Are you crazy?
You have to dig deeper before your support rate will rise.
Excavate first
Just flatten this place
Yes I know
Oops, that's a lot of money to do.
The money just keeps flowing, like water leaking
Flow non-stop
Let's go Yes
Tell you the next news
Booked a development site in Jangseokdong last night
There is a dispute between the contractor who wants to enforce the demolition and the residents.
A violent conflict broke out
including rights located on site
Candidates for Fengqin City Council included
More than a dozen residents were injured and sent to hospital for treatment
right candidate
Oh my god
Why are you here? Are you okay?
This one's not broken, just a little cracked.
Fortunately, the residents are okay
不是  就算你想保护大家
You can't use your own body to block it either.
Why do you have to do this?
Their problems haven't been solved yet?
Whether to develop Changshi Cave or not
Don’t 70% of the residents already agree?
Even so
But not most people’s opinions are right, right?
And surrounded by green space and water
The pollution problem is really serious
Most people want to develop it as early as possible
Live a happy life
You're blocking this thing
gold candidate
What do you think means living a happy life?
if we were like now
This continues to destroy nature
Human beings will eventually be unable to survive
Moreover, these residents
These people who were born and raised here
It can’t be like throwing away old things
Ignore them
Must protect them
If you are interested in becoming a city councilor in this area,
(Future Leap Forward Party)
Candidates Choi Woong-sik and Lee Min-jeon of Maheon City
(7 days left to local elections)
After successfully integrating
The gap in support will definitely widen
Choi Woong-sik is currently a candidate
People with a posture of 49.2%
Kwon Fengqin, the candidate with 30% support rate, was severely dumped.
Candidate Choi Woong-sik
The incident caused a storm in the city
Originally thought it might become a variable in this election
Unexpectedly, the support rate is still very stable
It must be stable
Please vote for candidate No. 1
"Look at me, look at me Choi Woong Sik"
Candidate No. 1 Choi Woong-sik
Cui Xiongzhi
thank you all
please take a look at this
do you mean
Are these all illegal activities committed by Choi Woong-sik?
yes that's right
Dear candidates
if we could put it together
I choose to exit
What? No policy consultation?
Just to simply disagree with someone's words
I don’t agree with coordinated qualifying
Also, this should call the police
Instead of relying on coordination to solve the problem
Then I'll leave first
right candidate
Then let's take a step first
No matter what
We have to stop Choi Woong-sik first, right?
I also think Choi Woong-sik should never be chosen.
That's right, candidates
If the three of us join forces
How much can it change the outcome of this election?
How is it
Let's join forces
Everything is integrated
"Qifeng, Qifeng, Quan Qifeng"
The electoral battle situation in Ma Xian City has changed dramatically.
The forced demolition of Changshidong last night was condemned
Candidates Lee Kwang-moon and Kim Wan-jae
It was decided to coordinate and the candidate Quan Fengqin will qualify.
Candidates Do Tae Woo and Lee Ye Seul
It was decided to join forces with candidate Shin Jae-yi
Stand up for him publicly
Prior to this, it had been successfully integrated
And candidate Choi Woong-sik, who has attracted a lot of support
Candidate Quan Fengqin is chasing him again
On the other hand
After the relaxation of development policies in Jangseokdong two years ago,
There are many large-scale
Development plans are underway
will be the key to this election
How strange
Why did Congressman Choi come to our store?
Do you want some fried chicken?
Fried better?
Looks like he wants to eat me
That 5.8% support rate?
You have to help our president lay out a picnic mat.
Please join forces with me
Then I can be elected right away
Oops, but 5.8% is not on the menu
It seems very expensive
I'm here for people who like to negotiate.
How could he come empty-handed?
Then
Just think that you support me
Please give up
There's not much here
But I have a condition
If you agree, I will support you
Oops, where are we going?
Just go here
Here? Yes
Wait
Are you waiting here?
sorry
because of my child
Terrible things have happened to you
Let me apologize to you on his behalf
please wait a moment
sorry
aunt
Also, please take a look at this one
Hyunwoo's mother
I'm Choi Woong-sik
I should have come to apologize in person.
But let me say hello to you first
I apologize to you on behalf of my son
Sorry, aunt
Be careful...
son
I already told the warden
Ask him to take special care of you
How are you doing?
And I’ll bring you the fried chicken you like to eat...
What kind of fried chicken?
Why are you apologizing to those bug-like guys?
So when are you going to let me out?
When...
so shameful
Why do you go around begging people to vote for you?
Dad
calm down
I...
I will let you out as soon as this election is over.
And those bug-like guys
I will also deal with them all. When?
When...
I'll let you out soon
why did you come here
I heard that you can't even eat well lately.
This is my opinion as a citizen of Ma Xian
If you are here to talk about coordinating the qualifying process
I'll take my leave now
Sorry
I withdrew my election
You are now...
Are you going to negotiate with me?
right candidate
Do you know what is most important in negotiation?
Just understand each other
Even if it's just a fried chicken
If you don't put your heart into it
It won't be delicious either
And I already understand your sincerity
take it
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
i support you
With candidate Shin Jae-yi suddenly withdrawing from the election
(1 day left to local elections)
The campaign just got more interesting
No. 3 candidate Quan Fengqin
Together with candidates Lee Kwang-moon and Kim Wan-jae
Fierce pursuit of candidate Choi Woong-sik
Candidate Choi Woong-sik’s support rate
It seems to be still stable so far
How will it develop?
for children's world
Let's go
Quan Qifeng...
The ever-changing election situation
As the two candidates compete fiercely
Candidate Quan Qifeng is launching a last-ditch battle on his own
The election campaign has entered its final countdown
What is the result is even more curious?
Quan Qifeng...
Hello, Master Jin
I need your help with something
Look at me Look at me No. 1
Candidate No. 1 Xiongzhi
Please vote for Choi Woong-sik
Look at me Look at me No. 1
Candidate No. 1 Xiongzhi
Please vote for Choi Woong-sik
briefcase with money
Give one to Prosecutor Zhang
Give the other to Chae Eui-soo, the owner of the car slaughterhouse.
It seems we have to lay an ambush to catch someone on the spot.
I know a hiding place where I won't be found
Hey, is this the one I'm talking about?
Yeah, that's the one you were talking about.
I had a hard time getting this.
Master Jin, thank you for your hard work.
Go to the refrigerator and get some cold drinks.
Big brother
Thank you for your hard work
It's not over yet
Isn’t the election campaign over?
There will definitely be good results this time
I have a strong feeling
what's going on
It's so unfaithful
Why are you two the only ones eating?
Brother, come here quickly
President Shen
Come and sit
Take a seat...
Very well prepared
Although he failed to stand for election to the end
But you have worked hard, right?
I can go here
Also experienced many difficulties
But
Just hold on until the end...
Candidate Quan is here just in time.
You are all already here
Yes, please come in
How could a candidate at this time...
No...
What's wrong...
Let me take a look
Here it is
Yedong Kwon Clan, Chung Yeol Gong Sect
38th generation descendants
The character is Feng
That's the kind of person I am
So that's it
Then I should be...
Here it is
The 35th generation is Qin
I am the 35th generation descendant Quan Fengqin
So...
great-grandson
yes
great grandfather
Brother Qifeng
Do you know what I hate most?
It's when people get together and fight to the death.
I really can't stand that kind of scene.
Isn't it? The two Yedong Kwon clans
The 35th and 38th generation descendants of the loyal father-in-law
great grandfather
Yes
I'll just...
Give in
Of course you have to give in
This book is really thick
thank you
Brother, don't cry
Then invite candidate Kim
Responsible for the business district that is less advanced. Okay
Jangseok-dong, old urban area, new urban area
Then let's start together
Just do it
Okay, let’s do our best together at the end.
Come on...
Come on
(Ryubon-dong No. 2 polling station)
Grandma, I went to vote first.
(Photography of ballot papers is prohibited at polling offices)
(Announcement of Candidate Withdrawal)
(Ma Xian City Councilor Election Quan Qifeng)
our choice
The 9th National Simultaneous Local Elections
The news coming at this moment
The ticket opening rate in Ma Xian City reached 99.3%
Is this election fraud?
Candidate Quan Fengqin of Tongqing Party confirmed to be elected
(Shin Jae-yi candidate 5.8%
Kwon Qifeng candidate 1%)
It turns out you want to eat it
My approval rating is 5.8%
I have a condition
As long as you apologize to the victims
I'll give you the 5.8%
Fried chicken shop owner, that bastard
(The 9th local election Magen City
Quan Fengqin was elected)
Mr. Cui Xiongzhi
I suspect you of violating public authority
Official Election Act and Abuse of Power
and various suspicions of accepting bribes, etc.
Arrest you urgently
What are you doing now? Wait a minute...
This seems to be some misunderstanding...
Hey, call the lawyer quickly and catch him.
Wait a minute why...
You can exercise your right of silence No...
everything you say now
It may become evidence in court in the future
You have the right to appoint a lawyer. Hello...
That hello...
Call a lawyer...
Hey, call Lawyer Park. Hey...
Call quickly. The phone can’t be reached.
Thank you for your hard work
Congressman, thank you for your hard work.
Rep. Kwon
Congratulations so much to you
Please let me pour you a glass of wine. Yes...
congratulations
Come everyone
Please do it for our sake, Mr. Quan Fengqin
Applause and encourage me
Everyone
We won this election together
Quan Fengqin...
It must be delicious
It must be delicious. Come on
To Ye Yeon
So delicious
Is it delicious? Yes
This is a taste you can’t get anywhere else
Where do you mean other places?
I don't know either
Every time my grandma eats this
They all say this
Ah...
I'm not saying this because I'm an employee
But the taste of this fried chicken is really nothing to say
Come on, give the last piece to Ye Yeon
How is it
Although it is the last piece
But it won’t become soggy
Still very crispy, right?
Yeah
Hey what are you doing
Let's go out and celebrate together
I really experienced something big this time.
Although it's a pity that you dropped out midway
But honestly
than being a city councilor
Fried chicken shop owner is more suitable for you
I think so too
Long Ba's father
Come to our house and kneel down to apologize.
thank you
This is all thanks to you two
Didn't I say it?
your power is very strong
He knelt down because he wanted to get your vote.
so amazing
Is that so?
Anyway
My first vote was a success
Because the candidate I voted for was elected
Uncle, I have something to give you
Huh? What?
you see
OMG...
Did you draw this, Yeyeon?
Who are these people?
This is my sister. This is my uncle.
This is Uncle Bili
Oh my God, the painting is so good.
Thank you Yeyan
Uncle, you not only helped me clip the doll
And the one who bullied my sister... But Yeyan
Uncle has given up holding dolls
By the way, Ye Yeon even helped her uncle paint his beard.
Yeah
come kids
Let's go out to celebrate together. Okay
Yeyan, let’s go, let’s go
(Congcong Supermarket)
On the eve of this local election
Current city councilors involved in multiple political scandals
was urgently arrested
Relevant persons involved in the case are being summoned one after another
Served three terms as city councilor of Machan City
Not long ago it was even possible
Choi Woong-sik, elected to the fourth term
Hurry up and think of a solution, Dad
(dock)
Why are you here now? Hurry up...
To date, there have been a total of seven charges
Has been charged by prosecutors
Not just involved in multiple political affairs
Former and current city councilman dealing with scandal
There are also entrepreneurs and prosecutors
and for his son Choi Yong-min
Faculty members covering up school violence
All were summoned one after another
Choi Yong-min, son of former Congressman Choi
Also suspected of attempted murder and abandonment of corpses
It has been transferred to the court. Oops...
This father and son really deserve it
people like them
It's a waste to feed the dregs from the prison to them.
Right bro?
Sister, I'm leaving first
What's wrong
Take a carton of milk and go.
No need
I just stopped by to watch the news.
I'm leaving
(National Forensic Hospital)
two days later
It's Xiaojun's birthday
And two days ago today
It’s Xiaojun’s death anniversary
Xiaojun's time
Stopped 15 years ago today
not only me
you...
This must also be the case
You will too in the future
Continue to live like this for the rest of your life
If your condition improves even a little bit
I will definitely kill you
(President Shin Project)
I was pretty confident about my search at the time.
dad
The memory is still fresh in my mind
What day is today?
Xiao Shen?
What's wrong? What's wrong with your eyes?
close your eyes
Is it a serial murder case?
Just the house you currently own
Just over ten buildings
I have already sent the official document this morning.
You should pack your things quickly too
Advance your flight tickets
I have a very nerve-wracking premonition
Those empty shell houses under Wu Meishu’s name
All the names have been changed.
Hello...
Chengmao